[
    {
        "question": "What is JavaScript?",
        "answer": ["A programming language", "Video editing software"],
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },

    {
        "question": "Is Earth flat?",
        "answer": ["Yes", "No"],
        "correctAnswer": 2
    },

    {
        "question": "Linux is?",
        "answer": ["Programming language", "Operating system"],
        "correctAnswer": 2
    },

    {
        "question": "Xbox is a console?",
        "answer": ["No", "Yes"],
        "correctAnswer": 2
    },

    {
        "question": "Android is based on Linux?",
        "answer": ["Yes", "No"],
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },

    {
        "question": "Free throw in basketball is worth one point?",
        "answer": ["No", "Yes"],
        "correctAnswer": 2
    },

    {
        "question": "ROM is a standard connector on PC?",
        "answer": ["Yes", "No"],
        "correctAnswer": 2
    },

    {
        "question": "What is ReactJS?",
        "answer": ["A JavaScript library", "Operating system"],
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },

    {
        "question": "Node.js is a JavaScript runtime environment?",
        "answer": ["No", "Yes"],
        "correctAnswer": 2
    },

    {
        "question": "Is Belgrade the capital of Serbia?",
        "answer": ["Yes", "No"],
        "correctAnswer": 1
    }
]